

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Mr M.Liria

NATIONALITY: Kenyan with UK permanent residence status

SUMMARY

A result driven, self-motivated and resourceful Quantity Surveyor with a career spanning almost 20 years of diligently managing construction costs and administering contracts for new build, planned and reactive maintenance works. He has extensive experience, mainly involving projects of up to US\$15 million in health, education, residential and office works for a wide variety of clients and employers in various local authorities, central governments and nongovernmental organizations (NGO's). His ability to communicate effectively with clients and contractors even as he works as part of a team or independently to enhance value for money while maintaining quality and standards gives me the confidence that he would be a valuable asset to any organization.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Building Economics (Hons)/ 1988-1991

EMPLOYMENT RECORD

- Infracost Consulting Ltd. (UK/ February 2013-July 2013/ March2010- August 2012)
 - Freelance Quantity Surveyor
- CTG Global Ltd/ International Organisation for Migration (Kabul, Afghanistan/August 2012 – January 2013)
 - Quantity Surveyor (Head of Cost Estimating Section responsible for construction of large hospitals, anti-narcotics centres, police training colleges, medical training centres as well as police forensics labs across Afghanistan)
- Amey Services Ltd (UK/ February 2009-March 2010)
 - Quantity Surveyor
- Systech Project Services Ltd (UK/ February 2008-November 2008)
 - Quantity Surveyor
- Ministry of Works and Transport (Nassau, Bahamas/ November 2005- November 2007)



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

- Quantity Surveyor
- United Nations (Trinidad and Tobago/ October 2004 October 2005)
 - Quantity Surveyor (As part of the United Nations engineering capacity building team assigned to Tobago House of Assembly, I was tasked with the reorganization of the estimating section at the Department of Infrastructure and Public Utilities.)
- The International Rescue Committee (Kakuma, Kenya/ April 2004- September 2004)
 - Construction/ Logistics coordinator
- Community Action Development Organisation (CanDo) (Kenya/ September 1999-March 2004)
 - > Construction Consultant
- Africa Education Fund International (AEF) (Ngara, Tanzania/ October 1994- January 1999)
 - Construction/Logistics Coordinator
- Ministry of Works and Housing (Samburu, Kenya/ September 1993 September 1994)
 - Assistant Quantity Surveyor

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Quantity Surveyor

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

- Professional Member of The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (MRICS) June
 2006
- Professional Member of Canadian Institute of Quantity Surveyors (PQS.) December 2012

N/A

LANGUAGES